const quiz3data = [
    {
      question: "__ President Clinton is to make a statement later today.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "The", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We usually use zero article before the names of particular people.'
   },
    {
      question: "Do you mean __ Ronald Reagan, or someone else?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'When we want to emphasize that a person is the one that everyone probably knows.'
   },
    {
      question: "__ Robinsons are away this weekend.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "The", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'The Robinson family.'
   },
    {
      question: "We arrived on __ Saturday as far as I can remember.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "a", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: 'We are only interested in the day of the week, not which particular Saturday.'
   },
    {
      question: "They arrived on ___ Saturday after my birthday party.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'A particular Saturday, specifying which one.'
   },
    {
      question: "We are going to a barbecue with ___ Simpsons.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'The Simpsons family.'
   },
    {
      question: "'When did you meet Sally?' 'In __ summer.' ",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'We use "the" when it is understood which summer, spring etc. we mean. (=last summer)'
   },
    {
      question: "I'll see you again in __ New Year.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: 'We say "in the New Year" to mean at or near the beginning of next year.'
   },
    {
      question: "We last saw David __ June your mother was staying with us.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "a", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: 'The specific June.'
   },
    {
      question: "__ school should be a place where children are taught to enjoy learning. ",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'We use zero article when we talk about institutions such as hospital, university, prison, school being used for their intended  purpose. '
   },
    {
      question: "Jane has gone to __ hospital to visit Joe.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: 'We use article when we talk about this as a particular place.'
   },
    {
      question: "Not many children enjoy __ opera.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'When we are talking about a form of art, we generally prefer zero article.'
   },
  ]
export default quiz3data
